Oh my god, the big guy has arrived.
The pilgrim has arrived.
Hi
[laughter]
Put it like that,
my
dance is great,
we are sharing love here
.
I'm also sharing.
What a blessing. [Screaming]
How was the Super America trip
?   I haven't
seen you for six months. I was so happy. I'm like this.
What is my daughter doing?
What is my brother doing?
Come and see for yourself.
[Music]
[Singing]
Now listen to the story you are going to tell.
[Music] A man is scared of a ghost.
He wants to know what's going on. Okay, don't be shy.
[Singing]
What a big guy. Look at the way he came. There was
a ghost in a village. That ghost
came from somewhere. It will
bite you and kill you
.  You're going to die [music].   Oh my
God,
everything will go to hell.  They wo
n't even learn to eat.
Why aren't you afraid?
Hey, that's my choice.
Hey, you four guys, go too.
[Music]
What's up, everyone?  Do
you go to the gym?  My
jungle is full of hands.  Come to the point.
Hey, hey, wait, what are you
saying to scare your kids? Mariamman, you're saying that they'll dance when you put the chicken in the pot. You're done scaring them. You're scaring them
properly. You
won't be afraid. If he changes,
he'll change.
Both of you, my sister and brother, go. In the
story we're going to tell, you don't
run around with your pants off.
First, fix your douchebag properly.
Oh, sir. It's
okay. Tell me the story.
A terrible little law [music] has come upon
me.
Why should I be afraid if I climb on you?   They do
n't step on you, they step on you.  Oh, Sarippa, there's
a little devil on you,
oh, on me, on you,
you don't know how to tell a story properly,
what a scary person you are.
[Laughter] They have a hole in their
ears that says they shouldn't tell scary stories to their children.
Sitting down,
Mom, I'm
watching now. There must
be a ghost. It's bothering
everyone. It's bothering everyone.
It's
eating everyone.  If you eat and go to sleep, my mouth will dry
up, my mustache will be wet, don't
you go, don't you go,
this guy, don't you
Why am
I running out of petrol?
Mom, Escape will
climb on me, you can handle it yourself.
As long as it's in my ear, no one can scare me. If you can't, try it.
This side vibes. Sister-in-law, stop being scared.
What are you lifting?
Even my brother won't look at you. Hey
[laughter] Don't be
scared. Mom, just climb on one of the bumps.
[screaming]
Just put a cow on it. Just scream and hit it.
[laughter] Come and see. Wait, wait,
mommy, I'm going there.
[screaming] You're laughing. Are you laughing? Sister-in-law is just like my
mother. Sister-in-law is just like my
mother. You're laughing. You're laughing. I climb on
anyone I see.
Look, I have to go home at 6:00 in the morning and
go to bed.
I have to wake up at 6:00.   I ca
n't do it. He
came and told me 20 days before my grandfather's 60th wedding anniversary
.  That's why I
came here.  I can't go back now.
Everyone has asked me to come, brother.
Vana Siddappa Jaliya may come and go.   Are
you afraid to fly? We're going to go by
car.  We'll listen to the song,
eat the delicious food, and then go to
Jaliya.
Your two daughters will love a house that looks more like your grandfather's palace than a mansion
.
Property is important to us.   The
unlucky clickbait is for cake.   It's
not enough to take the property and put it in the crematorium.  Sarima, can I come? My
uncle from here is coming.   If
my uncle's daughters don't come, I won't
come either.
You don't have to come.
Oh, how can I be so that I don't put it on? It
won't be a set for you.
I myself have
prepared everything, the shoes, the shoes, the shoes,
what are you doing?
I'm not using this,
this shoe, this shoe, this shoe, instead of
sleeping next to the bed, this shoe is the best.
Mommy, be proud of the growth of the baby.
[Laughter]
Total family damage.
Small shoes, why do you have such big shoes?
Aha. [Laughter] How can you
protect Sri Anjan and Prasanna Anjan from them?
Oh, Raga, Ragava, are you the only one who thinks like this, not like this, but like this, and
how can you
leave the grader like this? [Laughter] Why won't you
leave him alone?
He hasn't gone to the top yet?  Then I'll go
there too, I'll be the one to help you. I wo
n't sleep at night. If you want, I'll leave
my life to go away.
You, mother, take care of me.
Hey, you can at least watch him [ __ ]. Is that a
mistake?
You told me to go out like this.
You do
n't even want to come into the bathroom.  I don't want to go out of the bathroom.   There is no
need to sing a song.  I won't
go to the bathroom.
But I will go to Uchha.
How can I
put something like that on a typewriter,
brother?
That's not all,
Watchmen is an
old idea.
Then why don't
I go to the bathroom?  But I will go to
Uchha.
How is it?
I have a new idea.
What's the idea?   I wo
n't tell you, I'm lusting after you.   It seems like he'll
go wild [laughter] somehow.
Ready?
Ready, the
toilet next to the bed is new,
Emma, ​​I can't stand it, Emma, ​​I'm shaking my head, Papa, no
matter how they go, I
don't care, I'm going to Juja.
I don't want to wear sandals, I don't want to go to the bathroom
[laughter] I don't want to go to the bathroom, I don't want to go to the bathroom,
but I won't tell anyone
.  Promise,
promise,
small request, what's
this? It's been a day since I've finished it. I'm really scared.
Where are you running? [Laughter]
I'll sing a song, my
dear
Maria,
come and stand in the arena, don't you
see me? [Screaming]
This Punni, don't you
say that you are a grace puncher,
this world is fighting, keep fighting, keep fighting, keep crying, tell me, you are the one who told me, if she
breaks, go to town,
mother, is
he hungry? Has he started? Let's sit near the
water in some village and
eat.
That's why he has come to the village. Stop it, mother. He wo
n't stop. He vomited.
Stop it. He can't take it anymore. It's perfect. Come on, come on, come on.
There's a lot of garbage on the floor
.
What are you doing with your hands on your head?
[Music]
Hey, my dear, look up and down and
throw the dice.   I've been waiting for
a long time to eat,
but I can't eat here until the rain comes. I've
been waiting for a long time. I've been waiting for a long time. I'm waiting for a long time. Get up
, get up, go out, go out
.
Hey, what are you going to do?
Take the rope and
tie it tightly.
Pull and hold.
Hey, you have to work hard, right?
I was just hugging him.  Wait and
see.
Hey, don't drag me around without talking.   Please hit me with
something.   If there
was something to hit, why is this happening?
Someone must have driven a nail in just for us
.  Foot, foot.
Audio.
You are behind.
[Screaming]
Oh, wait, it's
raining.  Let's
climb.  Take two watermelons,
oh my, let's go as fast as we can, quickly   It's
a real commotion when the grandchild comes to say "Hi, grandparents" after the luggage.
Sir [music] The luggage
is in the check-in.   The name
Kokilam is to be
baked
[sneeze] Let it
be dark
[shouting]
[laughter]
Aunty, hello,
hello, uncle,
bless me Aunty, hello, hello, uncle, uncle, uncle, uncle,
mother, what is that? One uncle has a daughter up to
his knees, and
another uncle has a daughter up to his
knees. If one falls completely, he has
two
daughters. If someone comes next to him,
look, he
has no daughters.  I
wonder if Ivan will say hi from here instead of going to him.
Hi, I'm not
saying it's
perfect, but
where are the big ones?
Babyface
[Music]
Apoho [Music]
[Music] There are
many more, run, run, run, run,
Dad, Dad, why are you beating me?
What are you doing?
Stop it, won't you come when you come? You're calling my grandson and
beating me like this. I
won't pick up the phone, Grandpa.  Just one phone call and it'll be gone
.   Can't you just
make a phone call?   He's calling her, she's coming
.   I'll
call her and
tell her.  That's why I'll
call anyone.   Hey,
I have a
doubt about the matter.  Which of these three uncle's daughters have
you loved
so far?
This is where we will
make love.   The
groom's uncle
is waiting for three girls, including my two daughters and Kaviya.  Okay,
uncle,
okay, you three, don't you love only one of them, and the
other two won't get angry,
look here, grandma, we've been friends since we were little, let's
all take a sportive, let's
take a sportive, let's take a sportive,
but
this time, don't tell me who you love, that's all, okay, okay,
go get some rest, go and get some sleep,
like a mosquito swatting,
how did you come to get water, if I heard someone crying,
I would throw you out of fear
.
[Laughter]
What kind of young man
came to drink water alone in the middle of the night?
Atti, let me tell you something.
You didn't tell anyone about that.
What is it?
Grandma, there seems to be someone coming and going near that bridge.
[Laughter] When
I was in this house,
this was another room, the
basket only, there was nothing in this room,
you thought of something and got
scared, everyone in our house is
buying something like that, I don't know
where it is,
what's the noise, sir, what's wrong,
why is the tiki not damaged, what's wrong, tell me, papa,
he's scared of this noise,
everyone push me, I'll catch her,
hey [Crying] Come on, what's going on,
papa, what's coming, come on, I've changed
again,
I put it down,
who shouted,
why is all this in this house, go to him and
tell him, this is an illusion, there
is a Tulsi Puja in the morning, everyone go and
sing,
Srira [Music] Indira Shakthi
Puja
[Music]
Grandpa, it's only
60 years since the wedding for both of them.
Oh my god, you're standing there,
you and grandma, let's
do the aarti together.
Great idea. Let's do it.
I'm so excited.
Let's do the aarti with
your two eyes.
[Music] You
tied me up, you pulled me, it's not enough.
[Music] What's wrong with a
little smile?
Father and mother,
the story of the old man and the old woman, buying a good house, are you not a bad person?
After a long time, we
will all come together, right? It
will be a shame.
Hey Kumar, come and get the coconut and hammer it.
Hurry up and hammer it.
You know,
Bhagava, come down.
Okay,
Daddy.
[Laughter]
Look at your chest. It's so beautiful. It's so
beautiful. Enough of
playing. Stand up straight. Stand up straight.
You too, Mom. Wait. Wait.
[Music] The
mist is all gone. All the hands, feet, and
lips are gone. You just sit there. What can
we do now?
That's all. I've put my girlfriend in the bag.
[Music]
[Screaming]
We are the ones.  I'm watching you, I've watched   "
Come on, Kamakshi, take everything correctly and come, take a
step and come,
what is this, what is this, the touch pad and the
slippers are stuck in my hand, why don't you
wash them and touch them, no problem,
I am the one who stuck them,
this is my brother Raghavan's technique, maybe it has come,
first of all, I want to
know if there is a ghost or not,
I started the puja,
Om Muneeswara, our
mother,
hello, Nipadis, I
have touch pads in my hand."
Look at this, if anyone is dead, please tell me,
Kuppatha, it looks
like she's holding hands and coming here
.
Om Muneeswaraaya Namah
Account
sir,
have you arrived?
Come quickly and just drop it off
.   It seems like the
government is very aggressive
.
Next, you guys, get off.
Even if that ghost is idle, that horse wo
n't be idle.  Maybe the bust
check is over.
I joined the next bus, Flora Kutty.
Oh
my God, please take
care of me, I'm here
.
Why [laughter] Kapathukada,
how did I climb so high?
I climbed out of fear. Come
down anyway. I
know how to climb, but I don't know how to descend.
You, Jam Kapathukada
. There's a bad figure in the house, just like you said. Sami, protect me. I saw another close-up. Sami, yes, Sami, protect our mother, Sami.
Look, Sami, look, Sami, they're doing the same thing as when that ghost came to the house and licked the blood.
[Screaming]
Hi Sami, where are you going? Oh Sami,
Sami, come on,
my castle is full of
chaos. Sami [Crying] It's
like I'm getting a shock just to get the vibration. Come on,
Sami, come on, Sami, come on, let's go
home. Come on, let's go. I
need a girlfriend. [Laughter]
Because if I hang you up, I'm ready, but if
it's not there,
how can it happen if nothing happens tonight?  You're the one who sleeps every day
[laughter] Go to bed,
when did you start a romance and eat bloody food? I
thought,
brother, I have a problem with you at this time.
Yes,
brother, there's a ghost in this house,
someone keeps coming, going, coming,
both are the same. Is that the
same problem with us? We've been
talking about it.
A ghost just came and stood in front of me.
[Screaming]
Brother, whatever ghost we have, brother,
I'll see
what we can do now, brother [laughter] Shouldn't we go
to that Aghori? Don't hit
that Aghori.
I know a more powerful Aghori. Okay, okay, fight
with Aghori, fight with Aghori, fight with Aghori,
I won't worship you. Why do
n't you worship me? Brother,
brother, I'll go to Aghori and
say, "I'll go with you."  How did
you hide it?   Am
I awake or
awake?
Ushayiti Ushayiti Ushayiti
Hey, are you bothering me?
[Sighs] Can I
get some rice? Can I get a bowl of rice
?  No one is eating there.
A bowl of rice, rice [crying]
Can I get some rice, rice, rice, rice,
biryani? Yes, no one is eating there. Yes, I'm hungry. Go away, brother. Come on, brother. I'll go.
Brother. Go away. Come on. [crying] Nothing is
happening there. No one says anything to anyone.
Do you know how to pour the flour properly? I've
poured it. See if it's enough.
[laughter] [laughter
]
[screaming]
[laughter]
The old lady who was waiting for work pulled the bowl and poured the
flour.
You're laughing.
What's wrong, Udaar? We
came to tell you something important.
You were afraid and spilled flour into it.   It's not important, that's the
important thing
.   It
seems like the ghost in this house is still out.  Your boy is on top.
What is it?
Listen patiently to what we say.  Then
get angry.  Look, he's
putting on my allergies.  He puts on a trio of lipsticks
.  Here he is, wearing heels, slapping them
.
I don't understand anything you're saying.   I'm
scared.
Is there someone else inside him?
We're going to go and touch the glass.  Then whoever
is inside will definitely come out.   If you
tie him up today, the person inside
him will come out.
What is it?
The drama that is being created is like a hug,
but the truth of the drama will come out.  Is everything Mom
says true?
Yes, he has a lot of changes.
We have learned this only through our own practice.  I won't
tell you if you feel sorry for me.   Is
that so?
Yes.  [Laughter]
I'm so scared.
I won't believe everything you say about Raghav.
However, I agree with what you say
.
He will come now, just like we talked about this morning
.  Make him sit here and
the three of us will come to Kaglosa.
See if she will definitely come out.
Before he arrives, you should go there and
disappear.   Will all
this be okay?  I'm so scared,
what's going to happen?
Raghava
watches and leaves.  Sir, I need to
talk to you about something important.  A little
taxing?
I too have gone to important work
.   We've been
calling you, come and
sit down.
Take it.
Nothing, Raghav, there are only three of us
.  We can also come to your house.
You shouldn't come here, we're disturbing you
.   Look at
my eyes, Raga, all your
anger will go away.
Hey, how long have I been waiting for this?
Leave it.
[Music] Leave it. I won't leave it. I won't leave it. I won't leave it. Hey, hey,
the three of you have come
out with a plan. What are you doing? If
I come and hug your lover, will
you get angry or not?   I have
my lover inside me too.  The three
of you are hugging an apple together.
You are dolls.
Look at Sangam. Even if you rub it a thousand times, talk to it, hug it,
hug it, and
give it to me, "Umma, umma," I wo
n't be charmed by your makeup and beauty.  His
fascination is a stain on my beauty.   Do
you understand that
in front of my beauty, you three are
very afraid of being called bigots. I
speak softly.  do you know English I am
in love with Kali how dare you touch
him
you got the point
who is this Kali why did she do all this
the hell is happening why did she
buy your neck don't need
to explain it to you have avey iron
go and sleepy good night
baby uppa
that's what we said don't believe it now come and
look me in the eye come and ask me what's
going on like a doll this is Tamil you are the one
asking answer this meaning
what did this guy do is she
teasing you do you know do you know
everyone know?
Sir,
okay, I
heard this somewhere. Oh my, don't
look at my other face. Is it
another face? Where is my face?
[Screaming] A ghost hit me,
I don't know
why I hit you even after showing you my whole face. Why did you hit me? You're a
bad person, Sami?
Om Shakti Parashakti Om Shakti Parashakti Hara Hara Come out. Are you
calling anyone else? Empty.
[Screaming] Are you
calling anyone else to complain? What's wrong? Oh my.
[Screaming] Is another voice calling? Is
that even wrong?
You're asking.
This is a bigger problem. Sami,
tell me
who hit you.
We're not here. If she was behind the sofa,
she would have hit you. She would have died.
You're old. It doesn't matter if you die. We've
forgiven you. We got
married.  [Laughter] Can we
get a bag?
[Laughter] No, no, mom,
no  [Laughter]
Oh my
god,
[Laughter] he
sat in the middle.  That
devilish man, you are a
very bad person, Sami, you are a
very bad person, Sami,
you are a
very bad person, Sami, Sami, Sami,
you come,
little girl, thank you, thank you
[laughter] Don't be deceived, come here, I have been
taking the devil's beating for many years, there is no
discount,
you are the one who is in love, I will let you go, mother
[laughter]
Oh mother, what are
you doing standing there, come here
[crying]
That's
scary [laughter]
What, you called me to dance, you are just
dancing, are
you a little bit of a fool?
[Screaming]
Hey Moonjali, come here,
Om Shakti. [Laughing] Parashakti, Om Shakti,
Parashakti, Om Shakti, Parashakti, Om Shakti,
Parashakti.
[Crying] Are
you a ghost or am I a ghost?
You are you, you are you, you are me, stand back a
little, if
you turn around, I will hit you, even if you turn around, we will hit you,
what kind of song is there, standing there, pumping, no   I'm going out for
important work and
will make biryani when I return.
Sir, what will I do after seeing the trial that has come to our family?